Guide to the Association for Union Democracy: Women's Project Records WAG.331
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Subject and Organization Files, 1974-2004, 1947-2004 (Bulk 1980-2002); 14 Linear Feet
  - Committee for Humanitarian Assistance to Iranian Refugees (Includes Persian documents), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Education and the Workforce: Subcommittee on Employer-Employee Relations Hearing, Jun 1998 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Communications Workers of America: Local 1101 (Computer disk included), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Communications Workers of America: Local 1106, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Conferences (not Association for Union Democracy), 2000 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Consolidated Rail Corporation v. Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Contract Compliance, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Cornell University: the Institute for Women and Work, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations (ILR), 1989-2000 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Court Cases on Discrimination, 1990-2002 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Criminal Law Bulletin, Mar/Apr 2001 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Daphne Foundation, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Deer Creek Foundation, 1990-2001 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Democratic Socialists of America, 1966-1997 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Discrimination Complaint Forms, c. 1980s (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Directory of New York City Public Employee Organizations, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - "Dollars and Sense: Women and Work", 2000 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Drug, Hospital and Healthcare Employees Union, Local 1199, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - El Paso Community College: Women's Center Newsletter, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission v. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, et al., 1989 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA) - U.S. Fire Administration, 1993-1999 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Federal Employees, 1985-1988 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Federally Employed Women, Inc., 1991 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Florida Tradeswomen, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - "From Dreams to Reality Career Cards", c. 1978 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Fuerza Unida, 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising, 1987-1990 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Gaea Foundation, 1996-2001 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Gay Issues, 1989-1993 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Gloria E. Gonzalez v. New York Police Department, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - "Guide to the New York City Public Records": Courts, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Hard Hat News, 1989-1998 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Health Care Workers, 2000-2002 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Health and Safety Resources, 1999-2001 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Hiring Blacklists, 1981-1985 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Hiring Halls and Regulations, 1971-2001 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Hofstra University Institute of Applied Science, 1988-1991 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Home Care Workers, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - "How to Be a Carpenter Shop Steward" by Gregory A. Butler, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Hunter College School of Social Work: Education Center for Community Organizing (ECCO), 1994-1998 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - "The Impact of the U.S. Supreme Court Decisions of the Spring 1989 Term" - Panel on Employment Discrimination, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Impact Visuals: A Worldwide Collaborative of Photographers and Graphic Artists, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Indiana University of Pennsylvania -- University and College Labor Education Association -- Summer Institute for Union Women, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Institute for Women's Policy Research, 1989-2001 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), 1990-2001 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) & Union Local No. 3: Kelber, Laura Complaint against IBEW, 1987-1995 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) & Union Local No. 3: Lopez vs. IBEW and Union Local No. 3, 1986-1990 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) & Union Local No. 3: Molden vs. Dooley Electra Co., 1989-1992 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) & Union Local No. 3: Streeter, Ellington and Ellis vs. IBEW Local Union No. 3, et al. (I), 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) & Union Local No. 3: Streeter, Ellington and Ellis vs. IBEW Local Union No. 3, et al. (II), 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) & Union Local No. 3: Streeter, Ellington and Ellis vs. IBEW Local Union No. 3, et al. (III), 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) & Union Local No. 3: Women members list, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Third District Women's Caucus, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1984-2002 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - International Clerical and Bank Workers Conference, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - International Congress of Staff Unions: "Staff-Line", 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - International Labor, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers (IUE), 1992 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Jewish Women Foundation, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Job Discrimination, 1980-1989 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Jobs with Justice, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - "The Joint Employment Plan", undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Joint Industry Board of the Electrical Industry, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Joyce Mertz-Gilmore Foundation, 1982-1996 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Joyce Mertz-Gilmore Foundation, 1989-1994 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Kentucky Foundation for Women, c. 1986 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - La Mujer Obrera, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Labor Law, 1993-1998 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - "Labor Notes", 1990-1992 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - "Labor Notes": "Can Labor Change the World" Conference, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Labor Party Advocates, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Labor Studies Education Programs, 1986-1990 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - "Labor Today", Jul 1975 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Lesbian and Gay Labor Network, 1990-1992 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Lesbian Tradeswomen, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Lois Robinson v. Jacksonville Shipyards, Inc., 1992 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Lois Robinson v. Jacksonville Shipyards, Inc.: Appeal, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Long Island Tradeswomen, 1990-1992 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Long Island Women's Council for Equal Education, Training and Employment, 1991-1998 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Machine Action Project: "Still Trying to Make It Work: Women, Trades Training and Jobs", 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Maguire/Maguire, Inc.: "Workplace Campaign Marketing Kit", 1998 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Michigan State University: Clerical-Technician Union, 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Minnesota Women in the Trades, 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Mohawk-Hudson Tradeswomen, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Monarch Electrical Contracting Corp. v. Lillian Roberts, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Ms. News, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Mujer a Mujer, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - National Association of Women in Construction, 2000-2003 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - National Committee on Pay Equity, 1987-1991 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - National Council of Churches, 1979-1988 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - National Council for Research on Women, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - National Employment Lawyers Association (NELA), 1996-1998 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - National Employment Lawyers Association/New York: "Current Trends and Developments in Employment Law" Conference, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - National Organization for Women (NOW), 2000-2002 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - National Organization for Women - New York City (NOW-NYC): The Millenium Lectures (Audio available in OH83), 2000 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - National Postal Mail Handlers Union, 1989-2000 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - National Postal Mail Handlers Union: Women's Committee (Photographs included), 2000-2002 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - National Tradeswomen Conference (Photographs included), 1987-2001 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - National Tradeswomen's Network, 1990-1993 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - National Women's Law Center, 1989-2000 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - New England Labor Events, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - New World Foundation, 1999-2001 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - New York City Board of Education: Task Force for Nontraditionally Employed Women, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - New York City Coalition on Sexual Harassment: "Women Tell the Truth: A Conference on Parity, Power, and Sexual Harassment" Conference, 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - New York City Commission on Human Rights, 1993-1997 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - New York City Commission on Human Rights and the Office of Labor Services Hearings on the Extent of Discrimination in the Construction Industry, 1988-1992 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - New York City Commission on Human Rights and the Office of Labor Services Hearings on the Extent of Discrimination in the Construction Industry, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - New York City Commission on Human Rights and the Office of Labor Services Hearings on the Extent of Discrimination in the Construction Industry, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - New York City Commission on Human Rights and the Office of Labor Services Hearings on the Extent of Discrimination in the Construction Industry, 1990-1992 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - New York City Commission on Human Rights and the Office of Labor Services Hearings on the Extent of Discrimination in the Construction Industry: March 12, 1990 Transcript (I) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - New York City Commission on Human Rights and the Office of Labor Services Hearings on the Extent of Discrimination in the Construction Industry: March 12, 1990 Transcript (II) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - New York City Commission on Human Rights and the Office of Labor Services Hearings on the Extent of Discrimination in the Construction Industry: March 14, 1990 Transcript (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - New York City Commission on Human Rights and the Office of Labor Services Hearings on the Extent of Discrimination in the Construction Industry: July 10, 1990 Transcript (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - New York City Commission on Human Rights and the Office of Labor Services Hearings on the Extent of Discrimination in the Construction Industry: July 11, 1990 Transcript (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - New York City Commission on Human Rights and the Office of Labor Services Hearings on the Extent of Discrimination in the Construction Industry: Transcript, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - New York City Commission on the Status of Women, 1985-1998 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - New York City Commission on the Status of Women: Public Hearings on Sexual Harassment, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - New York City Commission on the Status of Women: "Women's Organizations: A New York City Directory", 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - New York City Council: Women's Issues Committee: Women in NYC Uniformed Service Hearing, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - New York City Housing Authority, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - New York City Office of the Mayor: Promotion of Equal Employment Opportunity in Contracts Awarded by the City of New York, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - New York Fire Department: Sexual Harassment, 1992-2001 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - New York Governor's Task Force on Sexual Harassment, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - New York Lawyer's for the Public Interest, Inc.: Sexual Harassment Legal Referral Project, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - New York Police Department, 1991-2001 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - New York Public Library Guild, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - New York State Apprenticeship and Training Council: Affirmative Action Report, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - New York State Attorney General Dennis C. Vacco's "Report On Gender Discrimination in the Securities Industry", 1998 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - New York State Division For Women, c. 1990s (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - New York State Division of Human Rights, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - New York State Governor's Task Force on Sexual Harassment, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - New York State United Teachers: New York Teacher, Mar 1993 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - New York Tradeswomen, 1989-1993 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - New York University School of Law: Public Interest Law Foundation, Inc., 1979-1990 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - New York Women's Foundation, 1988-1993 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Newsletters, 1991-2002 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Non-Profit Unionization, 1988-1990 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Non-Traditional Employment for Women (NEW), 1980-2000 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Non-Traditional Employment for Women (NEW), 1986-1998 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Non-Traditional Employment for Women Act (Senate Bill 975), 1989 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - North Star Fund, 1988-2002 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Northern New England Tradeswomen, 1987-2001 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund: Publications, 1990-2002 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Occupational Guides, undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Occupational Safety and Health Concerns (OSHA), c. 1985-1991 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Occupational Stress, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers (OCAW), 1973-1991 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Open Meadows Foundation, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Opening Trade Barriers Project, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Oregon Tradeswomen Network, 1991-1998 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Oregon Tradeswomen Network, 1991-1999 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Oregon Wild Conference, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - "Our Times", 1985-1987 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Paper, Allied-Industrial, Chemical and Energy Union (PACE), 2001 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Patterson, Brenda v. McLean Credit Union, 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Pay Equity, 1980-2002 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Pensions, 1975-1990 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - People of Color / Low Wage Worker -- Health and Safety Network, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Permanent Commission on the Status of Women (Connecticut), 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Philippines Workers Support Committee: "Philippine Labor Alert", 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Pillsbury - Green Giant Boycott, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Pittsburgh Opera Company: American Guild of Musical Artists (AGMA), 1983-1990 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Pittsburgh Opera Company: American Guild of Musical Artists (AGMA), 1988-1991 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - "The Plane Truth: a Newsletter by and for Airline Workers", 1991-1993 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Planned Parenthood: Worker Unionization, 1986-1989 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Plumbers, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Pride and a Paycheck, 1999-2002 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Printed Materials: Women Trade Workers, undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Pro-Choice March (Coalition of Labor Union Women/National Organization for Women, Inc.), 1992 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Puffin Foundation, Ltd., 1997-2001 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Punch Out: New York Labor, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Race, Class and Gender, Printed Materials on, 1978-1989 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Regional Labor Review, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Reproductive Health: Occupational Hazards and Rights, 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Reproductive Rights: Meetings and Union Lists, 1985-1989 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Republicans for Choice, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Resist (A Call to Resist Illegitimate Authority) Newsletter, 1999-2002 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Resist: Grant Applications, 1998-2002 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Rhode Island Working Women, 1988-1990 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - "The Rights of Employees and Union Members" (Giles, Larry M.), 1998-2001 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Robinson, Lois v. Jacksonville Shipyards, Inc., 1991 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund, 1989-2001 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Rutgers University: "Celebration of Our Work" Mentoring and Internship Panel, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Seattle Worker Center, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Service Employees International Union: Sex and Race Discrimination in Los Angeles County, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Sexual Harassment Clippings, 1983-2001 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Sexual Harassment in Higher Education, 1989-1992 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Sexual Harassment Law: Correspondence and Legal Cases, 1986-1993 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Sexual Harassment: Legal Resources, 1981-1991 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Sexual Harassment Pamphlets and Printed Materials, c. 1989-1993 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Sexual Harassment Reading Lists, c. 1992 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Sexual Harassment: Union Literature, 1981-2000 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Sexual Harassment Workshops, 1988-1992 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - The Sister Fund, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Sisters in Search of Transit Awareness (SISTA), 1993 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - "The Social Institutions of Occupational Segregation: Toward a Homosocial Theory of Sex Roles: An Explanation of the Sex Segregation of Social Institutions", undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Solidarity, 1991-1993 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Solidarity Committee of the Capital District: "Solidarity Notes" Newsletter, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Southeast Women's Employment Coalition, 1986-1991 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Stern Family Fund, 1997-2001 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Student/Worker Solidarity Committee, c. 1990s (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Committee On Employer-Employee Relations -- Committee on Education and Workforce -- U.S. House of Representatives, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Task Force on Sex Discrimination of Tradeswomen in Construction, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Tides Foundation, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - "Time for an Unjust Dismissal Statute in New York", undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Tompkins/Cortland Labor Coalition: "Central New York State Leadership Development Conference for Trade Union Women", 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Tradeswomen, Inc., 1983-1997 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Tradeswomen, Inc.: Trade Trax, 1984-1989 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - "The Tradeswomen Movement: Settling In", 1991 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Tradeswomen of New Jersey, 1989-1991 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Tradeswomen Now and Tomorrow (TNT), 2000-2002 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Tradeswomen Now and Tomorrow (TNT): "Building the Power" Conference, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Tradeswomen Now and Tomorrow (TNT): A National Conference of Tradeswomen's Advocates and Organizations, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Tradeswomen: Studies, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Tradeswomen.org, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Training Workshops and Seminars (Outside AUD), 1982-1996 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Transport Workers Union of America, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Transportation Workers Union: Local 100, 1990-2002 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Tri-State Economic Justice Network, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Trusteeships, 1980-2000 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Twentieth Century Fund, undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Union Elections, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Union/Labor Leaflets, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Union/Labor Publications, 1982-1992 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Union W.A.G.E. (We Advocate Gender Equity): "Talking Union: A Guide for Working Women" Pamphlet, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Unitarian Universalist Veatch Program, 1991, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - United Association of Plumbers: Local Union No. 1, 1998-2004 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers (UAW), 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers (UAW) Convention, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers (UAW) Convention, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers (UAW) Public Review Board: Annual Reports, 1992-1999 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers (UAW) Public Review Board: Appeals, 1994-1996 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers (UAW) Public Review Board: Appeals, 1997-2001 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - United States of America v. New York City Police Department: Settlement Agreement, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - United States Department of Labor, 1991-2001 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - United States Department of Labor: Equal Employment Opportunity, 1982-1989 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - United States Department of Labor: Publications, 1987-1999 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - United States Department of Labor: Women's Bureau, 1996-1998 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - United States Department of Labor: Women's Bureau - "Directory of Non-Traditional Training and Employment Programs Serving Women", 1991 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - United States Department of Labor: Women's Bureau - "Facts on Working Women", 1986-2000 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - United States Department of Labor: Women's Bureau - Labor Secretary Elaine Chao, 1994-2001 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - United States Department of Labor:Women's Bureau - Printed Ephemera, c. 1991 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - United States Department of Labor: Women's Bureau - Publications, 1980-1985 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - United States Department of Labor: Women's Bureau - Publications, 1986-1998 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Unites States Department of Labor: Women's Bureau - "Time of Change: 1983 Handbook on Women Workers" (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - United States Department of Labor: Women's Bureau - "Working Women Count! A Report To the Nation", 1994 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - United States Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - United Tradeswomen, 1989-1990, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - "United Tradeswomen: The Nuts and Bolts of Women's Grassroots Activism in the New York City Construction Industry, 1979-1984" (Masters Thesis), 2001 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - University of California, Berkeley: 3rd Annual Western Regional Summer Institute for Union Women, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - University and College Labor Education Association (UCLEA), 1992-2000 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Urban Justice Center: "Welfare, Workfare, and Jobs: An Educator's Guidebook", 1998 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Utility Workers of America, 1979-1990 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Wider Opportunities for Women, Inc.: Women's Work Force Network, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Women Electricians, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Women and Employment, Inc., 1985-1991 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Women Fighting Poverty Conference, 1997-2001 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Women and Foundations / Corporate Philanthropy, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - "Women In the American Welfare Trap", 1996 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Women in the Building Trades, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Women in the Fire Service, Inc., 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Women in Non-Traditional Work, Inc.: Tradeswomen of Philadelphia, 1988-1991 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Women in the Public Sector, 1985-1992 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Women in the Trades, 1988-1993 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Women in the Trades Conference (I), 1990 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Women in the Trades Conference (II), 1992 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Women in the Trades Conference (III), 1992 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Women in the Trades Conference: Printed Ephemera, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Women in Trades Fair, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Women in Trades, Technology, Operations & Blue Collar Work, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 1)